Thank you for watching!
You've got to do it!
Before you check out the cooking scenes of the members of Culinary Unknowns
Before you check out the cooking scenes of the Culinary Unknowns members, you can nominate ahead of time whose dish you would like to try.
No matter what the dish is
You must eat it no matter what the dish is!
The second half of the cooking project
Tonight's chefs are the four polar opposites.
This group is going to make sweet-and-sour pork and menjikatsu.
It's so hard!
No, it's very hard!
Difficult?
The tasting members only have to ask one question.
Can you find a member who looks like a good cook?
How full is your cupboard?
But maybe you don't live alone.
The cupboards at home.
Oh, yeah.
Wow, that would be bad.
I'll buy some, I'll buy some, I'll buy some
I'll buy it.
So you've been helping your mom?
That's okay, right? Regardless of whether you helped her with the dishes or not.
I mean, I helped around the house. All of it.
Yes. How about yoki?
If you do it, you get an allowance.
That's cute.
So, did you help out a lot?
When I was little.
When I was little, so I don't think I'd be cooking or bagging.
I don't know.
I did quite a bit.
I did.
But I understand.
He says he did.
I used to take care of my sister.
I took care of my sister.
Fear.
About the same as anyone else.
I don't know.
As much as anyone else. What about you? Do you think you've done enough?
I don't think I've done much.
Oh, come on, there's a lot of "as good as.
What was the first one?
I didn't do it.
I don't think I've done it.
It'll be bad when it's over.
I have no idea.
Wait a minute. I don't think we can all do it.
Maybe you're right.
I don't want to eat bad food.
I really don't.
Da-o, da-o, da-o!
Here's what the four of us nominated.
No Ogawa?
That's sad.
I thought Ogawa might not be doing it because I have an image of him as a tiny little guy who jumps up and down.
But I was so confused!
We're almost done with the cooking lesson.
Almost?
What a cute answer!
You haven't done it yet!
I knew the way you said it implied that you were helping out as much as anyone else.
I thought that meant you were cooking.
I can do it as well as anyone else, but I shouldn't answer that question.
I thought she meant it in that way.
Please.
And Kawasaki.
He said he has a younger son.
I thought she was cooking for him.
Is it fragrant?
Yes, it is.
I think everyone is too young for me.
I thought the subject was too difficult and Aya probably has never cooked before.
I thought Sakura and Satsuki would never cook either.
Even for those people...
Let's do it!
Let's take a look at the four of them.
It's hard to make sweet-and-sour pork, isn't it?
First, combine the meat and cut vegetables with seasonings.
Finally, add potato starch and seasoning.
The first one is the most popular, Ioki's Sour Pork.
onion
If you choose the right ingredients at a good tempo without hesitation, you can cut them with a good hand.
I cut it with a good hand.
It's just a cut!
I think I did something on a home economics test
I hate cutting onions.
I don't have goggles or anything.
I always get them from the swim kit when I'm helping out.
I know I've said this before, but I'm going to cut onions for the first time without goggles.
Is it pork feet for sweet-and-sour pork?
While saying "pig's feet", I cut the pork belly that I had already selected.
From my strange knowledge, I find potato starch and dip the pork directly into the potato starch with a little water.
That's amazing!
Next, Sugawara already knows what to do!
I think there's pineapple in it!
They've been saying that forever.
After the pineapple, the pork and vegetables are selected from memory.
And as I start to cut the ingredients, I realize something.
I should have had the sweet-and-sour pork.
I've never had it.
I'm going to make something I've never had.
Why don't you eat sweet-and-sour pork?
Next is the youngest chef Ogawa's Sweet & Snack Pork!
First, rinse the bell peppers quickly.
Do you want to hollow it out?
I did it with a stick!
I've never done this at all!
Following the cat's paw faithfully, we cut the ingredients as if we were crushing them!
After transferring them to a colander, we wash them a second time
Then I washed the carrots by themselves.
The carrot, which has been cabbed once on the side, finally breaks in two with the full power of a 15 year old!
That's scary!
I wonder...
I've never cooked Kawasaki's meat before, so I'm not sure which one I'm going to make next.
I've never cooked Kawasaki meat before, so I'm going to choose chicken thighs for my first meat dish.
I've never cooked meat like this before, so I'm going to choose chicken thighs for my first meat dish.
I managed to finish cutting all the chicken pieces with a saw-toothed knife... Wait a minute, this assembly...
What is this? It's vinegar-glazed pork.
Then, miraculously, the vinegar, which I recognized only by its appearance, is poured over the chicken.
To add flavor, we add this delicious-looking stuff.
It's going to be a hell of a dish!
It smells bad, but I don't hesitate to add Nampula. After that, I add more and more seasonings as I feel like it.
I'll mix it with this, but it looks so good when it's cooked!
When the mystery seasoning is ready, put the chicken in the marinade.
Iyoki puts the chopped vegetables on the fire and starts seasoning!
Let's add ketchup!
Mix in some Worcestershire sauce and it will be delicious!
After adding ketchup and Worcestershire sauce to the starch-pork mixture
This looks so good!
but it's not fried!
I didn't put vinegar in, I didn't put vinegar in, I added vinegar at the last minute, and the sweet and sour pork was completed!
Sugawara, who has never eaten Sour Pork before, begins to imagine what it tastes like.
I've seen it before. It's definitely different.
First of all, vinegar is poured into the pork.
Add oyster sauce to give it a brown color.
I'll add pineapple.
What's wrong, what's wrong, what's wrong?
Once I put the pineapple down, for some reason, I put a lot of potato starch directly into the pan
This is terrible!
Oh no, what should I do?
When it's in a bad state, put in the extra large pineapple and pork and heat it up!
Sliced! Pork slices!
Then, due to the effect of potato starch, a squishy substance is born!
Oh, lumps!
And the insane pork is ready!
Next, Ogawa neatly arranges the pork loin on top of the washed vegetables in its original shape!Ogawa then arranges the pork loin neatly in its original shape on top of the washed vegetables
What is this, a slice?
Are you barbecuing?
For seasoning, he added as much vinegar and soy sauce as there was in the bowl.
I don't know what "sweet-and-sour pork" is.
Ketchup?
Miraculously, ketchup comes to mind, and we put in all the ketchup we have.
After that, I fry it slowly until I'm satisfied with it, and the Sushi pork is ready!
I also added two tomato vinegars!
And now, let's continue with Kawasaki, who is showing us the cooking from hell!
I wonder what "Sour pork" is.
I wonder if it's okay to put sauce in it
Again, I chose Worcestershire sauce based on its appearance and blended it with the vinegar-cured chicken to add a little extra seasoning.
It's still a mixture of many flavors all the way through.
Sauce pork, now, right?
Chicken.
Ah chicken or sauce chicken.
And then the messenger from hell turns his attention to the next one.
I'll put a little flour in it.
I'm eating flour.
I'm going to put a lot of flour directly into the chicken.
Looks like cheese.
Looks delicious!
And add a lot of potato starch, too.
Double flour!
Why add potato starch?
It hardens.
I think I have some sweet and sour pork.
I want to add something red.
And I'm going to add tomato sauce.
It's delicious.
This sesame oil.
I often put sesame oil in various dishes.
I'm not sure what to do with sesame oil.
What do you think?
I put sesame oil in the pan and stir-fry it.
Kawasaki's Sweet & Snack Pork is ready!
So far, I haven't had a single one.
That's great!
I knew Ogawa was small and I could see through him.
I see...
But we're all at the same level.
He puts potato starch right in.
They have absolute faith in katakuriko.
Next, the four of us made minced pork cutlets.
The key is to put the batter on the chopped onions and minced meat in the right order and deep fry them
The key is to apply the batter in the correct order and deep fry them!
Let's start with Sugawara's cooking.
First, select ground pork as opposed to ground beef.
He takes the time to remove the shells.
However, when the onions, ground meat, and eggs are kneaded well, the meatballs are made into giant softball-sized dumplings!
First of all, I kneaded a huge meat ball the size of a softball.
Then the batter is applied in the order of egg, flour, and breadcrumbs.
Sugawara, who has no concept of frying here, bakes them without hesitation.
He puts oil on an unheated frying pan and waits forever for it to bake.
Sugawara's grilled menchikatsu is ready!
Next is a nice big menchikatsu!
Don't eat it as it is!
But it smells the most delicious even if you eat it raw!
Let's put it all in for now!
First, combine all the ground meat you see!
I wonder if there is any seafood in it.
I don't think so.
It smells delicious!
Without knowing the basics, the chef, on a whim, chopped up everything that he thought looked good and put it in.
For some reason, I'm going with the basic salt and pepper seasoning.
Dip it in flour, then in egg, then in flour.
Thanks to you, I've helped out.
Thanks, mom.
That was helpful.
Thanks to you, when you put the batter in the perfect order, it starts to look pretty much like that.
And then we finish it off in deep-frying style!
With the mysterious technique of a French chef
Iyoki's menchikatsu is ready!
Here is the youngest Ogawa's menchikatsu!
First of all, he uses a small spoon to transfer the minced meat to a bowl...
I'm so anxious!
I'm mending
I'm mending!
Menchi-ing the minced meat
I've heard of summer stew
I'll go put some in.
A little bit is fine
We use a unique seasoning called "Natsumegu
We season it with a unique seasoning called Natsumegu.
And oil is a blend of salad oil and sesame oil.
I shake the pan and bake it.
And when it is covered with direct breadcrumbs without flour from the egg
and put it on.
These are going to peel off.
I didn't turn on the fire.
Oh, man.
Oh, my God, I almost forgot.
You're putting it in?
Oh, man.
Dive into room temperature oil and continue to fry slowly.
Ogawa Menchi is complete.
And finally, we have the chef from hell, Kawasaki.
It's got a name.
There are four colors!
What am I going to do with this one, pick your favorite color!
From the four colors of Oni!
Beef shanks are being cut up guillotine style!
I don't know what I'm making.
I'd like to add some flavor to it
Go for it!
Oh! It smells like mentsuyu!
Let's put this in for now.
Here.
Men-tsuyu is so versatile.
I want to put it all in!
Seasoning is in hell mode again!
Seasoning with a lot of seasonings.
Shape them with potato starch and deep fry them.
First of all, let's make the hellish meat ball onigiri.
Sprinkle katakuriko on the top of the rice ball, and sprinkle bread crumbs on the top.
And sprinkle bread crumbs on top.
If you think about it, you'll understand
It would be better to put them in the bat and roll them
Why sprinkle from the top?
I can't get it to stick.
It's an egg, it's an egg.
Like Ogawa here
If you start with room temperature oil
Oh, from room temperature!
I'm getting oil all over the place.
There was powder on it, but it's gone!
The batter is instantly stripped off, and the menchis are added one after another!
Oh no!
The batter is gone!
What can we do?
What shall we do?
Let's put all of this in to make it look like batter!
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, man, you're a hell of a cook, you know that?
It's not gonna stick if we put it in here.
It's gonna stick around.
And here we have Kawasaki's Jigoku Menchis, which are supposed to be crispy and crunchy on top.
Kimura, this block is a mess.
There's no one here.
Awasaki, you got cheated.
You'll be looking at this differently from now on.
It's true.
First, let's sample the most popular dish, Iyoki's.
Here you go.
Yum... Yum.
Delicious!
Yum! There it is!
Sour pork!Eh, sweet & sour pork!
It's delicious!
It's actually Sour Pork!
It's just that it's more matte than the Sour Pork I know.
I know shinier ones.
Then the minced meat!
The mince is very minced too.
Very minced!
I didn't know it was so minced!
Delicious!
There it is!
It's delicious.
Crunchy, too.
Here it is!
Shokichi's Sweet & Snack Pork and Menchi-Menchis!
Shall we go?
Open, Zan Dong!
Wow, it's yellow!
Wow!
It smells like food scraps!
Ugh!
What is this?
It really smells like garbage.
It smelled amazing when I was making it!
Ugh!
It's really a sour garbage smell, so I can't stand it right away!
This is Sour Pork Sauce Pork Shokichi made!
A boy who has never eaten sweet-and-sour pork before...
Bon appétit!
Oops, for some reason
Oops... I'm getting a little carried away.
What do you think?
Pineapple saves the day.
Oh, good, you're in.
I can't get in.
Oh, man, I'm starting to get tired of you, Hiro.
It's really making me sick.
I think I did a good job with the batteries.
It's like a thick, grilled rice ball.
What do you think?
There's no taste!
Oh, my God.
It's not that bad, but...
It's just a piece of meat.
Why do you only taste it?
Why did you clap your little hands?
No, he said it wasn't bad.
Next, Ogawa, who was not nominated
tasted it himself.
What's this?
You just made this?
It's so old, it's like it's been handed down from generation to generation.
It's true!
I'm scared.
Ew.
That's not good.
My body is reacting falsely.
It's true.
And Kawasaki's hell food is Kanagawa's tasting!
Ouch!
It's delicious!
Yuck.
I said it's good.
Delicious!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
I'm laughing.
I just said it's good, and you said it stinks.
It's always stinky, it's always stinky.
Wait a minute!
You don't have a bamboo shoot, do you?
Miracles are made up of a bunch of miracles.
No way!
Then let's try the munchies!
This takes a lot of courage.
I started at room temperature.
That's right.
It's big.
You're not eating rice cakes?
LOL!
I'm sorry.
That's not why we're here.
What's that?
You're looking for good food.
It's okay if it's not good.
Don't bench me.
I don't want to do a second one.
He's really funny.
I don't mind.
I don't think you have to be a good cook.
I don't know, it's just... it pisses me off.
To be honest, only the sanity island
It's just plain bad.
It was really bad.
I wish they'd serve it at the Nogizaka Cafe.
That's a good idea. That's a good idea.
I wish they'd make bentos for everyone.
Before a show or something.
Sankeiji made it today.
Bento.
Shoji's lunch box
I like oyster bento.
Let's see... Suzuki...
The graduation concert is over
Is it your last job?
It's time to go
That's right
Suzuki was like a doll at first.
She was the most reticent member.
I tried not to make eye contact.
I thought if I made eye contact, I'd get talked down to.
I've changed a lot.
I mean...
No matter what I ask, it's like...
At first, right?
I was scared.
I was probably too old then.
I was still young.
The first time I heard something like, "I like airplanes.
What? Airplanes? What do you like about airplanes?
It's fine.
It's good. It's good.
It's okay.
I'm asking you because I said so.
But, you know, you'll get used to it.
In the second half of the show, if I shake him, he'll talk a lot.
I really enjoyed it.
Ten years, right?
That's sad.
Please don't say that.
I'm so happy.
It's true... you and Suzuki are in a different marriage.
It's true.
I got hit by a lot of guys.
It was the worst.
You were good at catching water balloons.
You've got an interesting character, don't you?
Yes, in that way.
I'm very happy.
Do you have any memorable moments?
On the show.
The thing that really made me happy was last summer's national tour.
You came to Hokkaido, right?
The picture of the shadow hole at that time.
I've kept it as a treasure.
I'm so happy for you.
We took a picture of the three of us like this.
So, to the fans...
Please say hello.
We saw a lot of you during the construction in Osaka.Osaka under construction and a lot of appearances
I've shown you a lot of them.
I myself have discovered a lot of new things about Osaka.
I think it was a program that allowed me to discover various charms.
I'm sure you'll be able to see a lot of that side of me
I'm sure you'll be able to see a lot of that side of me too.
I hope you will continue to enjoy
I hope you will continue to enjoy watching the show.
Thank you very much.
Commemorative gift for the assault
Here it is.
A paperback book cover.
Since you are a voracious reader
I'm very happy.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Matsumura Ikuta's Graduation Concert
Blu-ray & DVD
Blu-ray & DVD of Matsumura & Ikuta's graduation concert will be on sale!
Asuka Saito Graduation Concert
Second round of selection is now open!
I'm Aine Suzuki.
Fighting too?
Please subscribe to our channel.
I don't think I can do this.